<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dockerfile on Anand vyas</title>
    <link>https://anandvyas.in/tags/dockerfile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dockerfile on Anand vyas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anandvyas.in/tags/dockerfile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Compose</title>
      <link>https://anandvyas.in/docker/docker-compose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anandvyas.in/docker/docker-compose/</guid>
      <description>The Compose file is a YAML file which defines services, networks, and volumes. Compose file is located at the following path ./docker-compose.yml.
Docker-compose Terminal Commands docker-compose logs Displays log output from services.
# Display the log of service containers docker-compose logs web  docker-compose ps Lists containers.
# Display the list of total containers which are defined in docker-compose.yaml file docker-compose ps  docker-compose scale Deprecated You will scale from the docker-compose up scale web=3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dockerfile</title>
      <link>https://anandvyas.in/docker/dockerfile/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anandvyas.in/docker/dockerfile/</guid>
      <description>A Dockerfile is a text document used to create own docker container. A Dockerfile has some commands
 FROM: Sets the Base Image for subsequent instructions. MAINTAINER: (deprecated - use LABEL instead) Set the Author field of the generated images. RUN: execute any commands in a new layer on top of the current image and commit the results. CMD: provide defaults for an executing container. EXPOSE: informs Docker that the container listens on the specified network ports at runtime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>